let questions = [{
  "numb": 1,
  "question": "Scarcity of food is a",
  "answer": "push factor",
  "options": [
    "chemical factor",
    "demographic factor",
    "push factor",
    "pull factor"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 2,
  "question": "Good climate is a",
  "answer": "pull factor",
  "options": [
    "chemical factor",
    "demographic factor",
    "push factor",
    "pull factor"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 3,
  "question": "The movement of individuals away from their place of birth or hatching or seed production into a new habitat or area to survive and reproduce is called",
  "answer": "dispersal",
  "options": [
    "translocation",
    "migration",
    "dispersal",
    "drifting"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 4,
  "question": "\"The geographical distribution of a species will be controlled by that environmental factor for which the organism has the narrowest range of tolerance.\" This is the statement for",
  "answer": "Shelford’s law of tolerance",
  "options": [
    "Liebig’s law of the minimum",
    "Liebig’s law of the maximum",
    "Shelford’s law of tolerance",
    "Shelford’s law of intolerance"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 5,
  "question": "\"Quick movement over large distances, often across unsuitable terrain\" is a description of",
  "answer": "jump dispersal",
  "options": [
    "diffusion",
    "secular dispersal",
    "jump dispersal",
    "drifting"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 6,
  "question": "The regular, seasonal movement of animals, often along fixed routes is called",
  "answer": "migration",
  "options": [
    "translocation",
    "migration",
    "dispersal",
    "drifting"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 7,
  "question": "The movement of lions across the Gir landscape is an example of",
  "answer": "diffusion",
  "options": [
    "diffusion",
    "secular dispersal",
    "jump dispersal",
    "drifting"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 8,
  "question": "Which of these is not a physical factor of habitat?",
  "answer": "predators",
  "options": [
    "soil",
    "moisture",
    "predators",
    "temperature"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 9,
  "question": "Transplantation experiments are used to find",
  "answer": "potential range",
  "options": [
    "potential range",
    "effective range",
    "actual range",
    "economic range"
  ]
}
,
{
  "numb": 10,
  "question": "I tried growing vegetables under my teak plantation, but the vegetable plants died out. I should be concerned about",
  "answer": "allelopathy",
  "options": [
    "autophagy",
    "allelophagy",
    "autopathy",
    "allelopathy"
  ]
}  ]